

## **Profile**

Experienced Full Stack Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology, services and product industry. Skilled in JavaScript, Angular, React, React-native, NodeJS, MongoDB, Cordova, Ionic, and JS technologies. Strong engineering professional with a Master of Computer Applications (M.C.A.) focused in Computer Science from Babasaheb Bhimrao Ambedkar University.

## **Internships**

Software Developer Intern, Aspire Software Solutions, Ahmedabad

JANUARY 2017 - JUNE 2017

## **Employment History**

Full Stack Engineer, Roambee, Ahmedabad

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

Working with roambee's costumer-centric team to make the website better and more feature-rich.

Associate Software Engineer, Knowarth Technologies, Ahmedabad

JANUARY 2020 - MARCH 2020

Worked in building company internal project "key performance indicators dashboard"

Associate Software Engineer, Aspire Software Solutions, Ahmedabad

JULY 2017 - DECEMBER 2019

As a service based industry, here I got a chance to work on multiple projects covering quite interesting domains and technologies

## **Projects**

#### Asset and Shipment Tracking Module (Roambee)

MARCH 2020 - PRESENT

Working on asset and shipment tracking module to give a detailed view of customers shipments and their assets using Google Maps, Leaflet and deck.gl

#### Viral Muni (Self)

JUNE 2020 - NOVEMBER 2020

Took part in Digital India AatmaNirbhar Bharat Innovate Challenge and built a web and mobile based news application that uses cutting-edge technology to recommend the most relevant and interesting news individually to each use.

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.viralmuni

#### **Covid 19 India Tracking Portal (Self)**

APRIL 2020 - APRIL 2020

Built a web app as a hobby project for tracking covid-19 infection rates in India

#### **KPI Dashboard (Knowarth Technologies)**

JANUARY 2020 - FEBRUARY 2020

#### **Details**

9140940053

ashutosh.shukla.7246@gmail.com

#### Links

Linkedin

Git

#### Skills

HTML & CSS

**JavaScript** 

Typescript

Node.js

Angular 2+

React

Git

MongoDB

**React Native** 

Ionic Framework

Docker

Elasticsearch

Redis

Amazon AWS

#### Languages

Hindi

English

#### **Hobbies**

Product development, Geopolitics, World affairs, History, Music, Cosmology Built a web app for project key performance indicators dashboard

# Data assessment(workday data) for Finance and human resource management Platform (Aspire Software Solutions)

MARCH 2018 - DECEMBER 2019

Built and web app for assessment of raw workday data and provide a meaningful data in form of graphs and generating recommendation according to it

#### **Social Crowdfunding Portal (Aspire Software Solutions)**

JANUARY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2018

A social crowdfunding platform for supporting projects in the creative arts and films

#### **Draw based Lottery Application (Aspire Software Solutions)**

JULY 2017 - JANUARY 2018

A mobile application, which is focused on the principle of a Raffle Draw.

#### **Corporate Data Store (Aspire Software Solutions)**

JANUARY 2017 - JULY 2017

A web application for showing collection of valuable authentic corporate information on each and every Indian Corporate entity made available to one and all its visitors and creates a huge informal network of all Entrepreneurs, Investors, Professionals and Managers that portrays a connected to customer's firm in India.

## **Education**

#### M.C.A., Baba Saheb Bhimrao Ambedkar University, Lucknow

2014 - 2017

#### B.Sc., University of Lucknow, Lucknow

2011 - 2014

## **Strengths**

Resilient, Self-Learner, Creative, Self-Confident, Risk-taker, Optimist, Contented

### Weeknesses

Impulsive, Mono-Tasker, Stickler, Bigot